glossyplay.com 2019-04-15

# Privacy Policy | GlossyPlay - It's a glossy experience!

## Privacy Policy

Introduction

This privacy policy was last updated on November 13th of 2018.

The GlossyPlay.com website and games published by it (developed by us or external developers) (further called GlossyPlay, or product) and other services used by GlossyPlay collects data from users that play them (further named „you”) to help us improve our entertainment products.

Visiting the website or playing the games implies you have agreed with this Policy and have read it. You might need to return and check the Policy periodically as we may modify it without prior announcement. Children under 13 years old must be supervised by an adult that is solely responsible for reading and accepting this policy.

Personal information

GlossyPlay may collect the following information about you: 

the emails you send to GlossyPlay;

the messages you send GlossyPlay on Facebook, Twitter and any other social channels GlossyPlay is officialy represented on;

the forms you fill on our websites or using our products;

statistics about the way you use our products, what devices or software are you using as well as visits, game progress and any other details that help us understand you as a user of our products (this information is not linked to you as a person, it is anonymous and we use it for the sole purpose of improving our services);

data that third parties might share with us intentionally and with your consent;

We may use the above­mentioned data for the following purposes: 

fixing and improving our products and services;

support – we may contact you or respond to your messages in order to solve your issues regarding our entertainment products or help you use them;

administrative issues such as Terms of Service violation;

crime, fraud and any other purposes that might serve the Law and is required by it.

Some of the website's features and games might use third party services such as Facebook or other social networks with prior notification. You can stop information from being shared by adjusting your settings on the respective social media account.

GlossyPlay will not take responsability for any information you share on Facebook or other social media networks using website's features or games.

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our product and servicing you in using our websites or playing the games.

We may keep a record of your information after you stopped using our products. We will only use that information according to this Policy and if you do not agree with this you can let us know at eve@glossyplay.com and we will delete your information.

We provide a secure environment to protect your data from being hacked, stealed or disclosed by third parties without your consent. Your information is hosted on our servers, only accessible to a limited number of individuals with special rights, and is considered confidential. However, we cannot guarantee a perfect security system. 

By using our products you agree to let us use this information as explained above.

You may request a copy of your data by contacting us.

Cookies

Cookies are small files that are stored on your computer carrying data to help us remember your previous activity in order to improve your experience. Cookies cannot give anyone access to your files or any other activity but the use of the websites it was designed for.

You can learn more about the cookies we store and how we use them by reading our Cookie Policy. 

Advertising

GlossyPlay may use ad network providers, ad exchanges and ad servers through Advertising Partners to help present advertisements on the websites and in the games. These Advertising Partners use cookies for presenting, better targeting, and measuring the effectiveness of their advertisements, using data gathered over time and across their networks of web pages to determine or predict the characteristics and preferences of their audiences (further named Advertising Data). GlossyPlay will process such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Our Advertising Partners may act as a data processor or data controller with regards to the Advertising Data, depending on the scope of their services. The Advertising Partners are responsible for their compliance with the applicable data protection legislation. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by such third parties as ad network providers is subject to their own privacy policies, not this Privacy Policy. 

You can choose what Advertising Data we store and use by visiting our Cookie Policy. 

Safety

Appropriate measures to safeguard, maintain data security, and prevent fraud were taken to assure the best possible protection for you when playing our games. However, posting personal data, sending us sensitive information or making any other information public on our website or games, through our products or on our social media network pages/accounts is at your own risk.

We cannot modify or delete any information you shared on Facebook or other social networks where GlossyPlay might be represented. The information you share is your responsibility.

After we delete your information, some of it might still be available through archives and cached data that is not controlled by us.

You must be aware that our products are designed to be used by users over 13 years old. Children younger than 13 years old should use our products in the presence of an adult.

We are not responsible for any sensitive information that was shared using email, social media, comments or any other method by an unsupervised child.

Our products may contain external links and use external services that are subject to their own privacy policies. When you leave GlossyPlay, you must know that we no longer have control over the content or data of other websites on the internet and you should use them at your own risk and applying their policies.

Conclusions

If some of the terms this Policy presents is proven unenforceable by any competent authority, the remaining terms will not be affected by this decision.

Agreement

By using GlossyPlay Products you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use GlossyPlay products. We reserve the right to make changes in this policy at any time. Please check the policy each time you use our web site to ensure you are aware of any changes in our privacy practices. Our privacy policy will indicate the date it was last updated.

We will try to create the best possible experience for you by constantly improving our products and delivering high quality services. Enjoy playing on GlossyPlay.
